Guide to the Roy Lee Williams papers 1974-1983 IBT0027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Roy Lee Williams papers
1974-1983
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0027
12.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in its original order. Further processing will sort the materials into series to be determined later.
Biographical / Historical
Roy Lee Williams, born March 22, 1915 – April 28, 1989, was an American labor leader who was president of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters from May 15, 1981 to April 14, 1983.
Roy Williams began working as a truck driver in 1935 and was elected business agent of the union's Wichita, Kansas local in 1948. He later was elected president of Joint Council 56 and president of Teamsters Local 41 in Kansas City, Missouri.
Prior to holding the position of General President Williams was the Director of the Central Conference of Teamsters, during which time he was forced to resign from the Central States Pension fund after the US Department of Labor sued him and four colleagues for violating their fiduciary duty. Williams was elected General President of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters 1981, but was forced to resign his presidency early after being convicted of conspiring to bribe Nevada Senator Howard Cannon to defeat a trucking deregulation bill. He died in April of 1989 shortly after being released from prison.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of files from former IBT General President Roy L. Williams' Kansas City office, produced during his tenure from May, 1981 to April, 1983.
The largest section of this collection is a variety of correspondence. The majority is correspondence with IBT employees, IBT joint councils and union locals, and transportation companies. The collection also includes correspondence files relating to specific subjects, such as the Central States Pension Fund and National Master Freight Agreement negotiations, and clerical correspondence relating to the operation of the Kansas City office.
In addition, the collection contains various materials detailing the state and operation of the union during Williams' tenure. These include reports, financial information, General Executive Board meeting material, and subject files on such topics as trucking deregulation, out-of-work benefits and pensions. Of particular note here are the materials detailing the National Master Freight Agreement negotiations, the IBT Democratic, Republican, Independent Voter Education (DRIVE) program, and UPS Master Agreement Contract negotiations.
Of particular interest in this collection are materials detailing the major controversies which marred Williams' presidency, namely the United States vs. Dorfman, et al bribery case, for which Williams would eventually spend three years in prison, the United States vs. IBT Local 560, et al labor racketeering case, which sparked a Federal effort to mediate the influence of organized crime on labor unions. Included here are case files, hearing transcripts and correspondence.
Completing the collection are a variety of miscellaneous materials, including news articles and paper clippings, materials from the inauguration of President Reagan in 1981, holiday cards, blank forms, and drafts of the International Teamsters magazine.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor and laboring classes; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
- Correspondence: Jack (John) Sullivan [1/4], 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Jack (John) Sullivan [2/4], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: Jack (John) Sullivan [3/4], 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Jack (John) Sullivan [4/4], 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Regan's "War on Regulation", 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Trucking Deregulation, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Labor Department - Unemployment and Budget, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Victor Riesel - News Articles, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Democratic, Republican, Independent Voter Education (DRIVE) Program, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Home Mortgage Loan Program Proposal, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Letters to President Reagan, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Meetings with President Reagan, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Republican Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Reagan Administration, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reagan Inauguration Ceremony - Program, Schedule, etc., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Department of Legislation and Political Education Report, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Vice President Bush, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- IBT Group Insurance Plan and Forms, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Harold Gibbons, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Roster Changes, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Hobbs Act Legislation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- No-Raid Pacts, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: International Office, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondence and Report re: Airplanes, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Monthly Per Capita Reports, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- IBT General Organizers, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Robert Baptiste, Labor Counsel, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Eugene Burroughs, IBT, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Edward Charnock, IBT, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Correspondence: Aruthur Kane, IBT, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Joseph Townsley, IBT, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Rolland McMaster, General Organizer, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Bartley O'Hara, Legislative Counsel, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Bill Pugh, IBT, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Ray Schoessling, General Secretary-Treasurer, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Walter Shea, Executive Assistant, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: David Sweeney, Director, Legislative Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence: Rudy Tham, International Representative, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Roland Wilder, IBT, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: Norman Weintraub, Chief Economist [1/2], 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Norman Weintraub, Chief Economist [2/2], 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: M.E. Anderson, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: Charles Thibault, President, Canadian Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Joseph Morgan, Vice President, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Louis Peick, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Donald Peters, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Jackie Presser, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Joseph Trerotola, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Correspondence: Arnie Weinmeister, Vice President, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Barbara Hoffa Crancer, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Jolley, Moran, Walsh, Hager and Gordon, Attorneys, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Barbeau Roy Resume, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Harry Browne, Attorney, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Barry Levine, Attorney, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Correct Letter Headings, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Correspondence re: Requests for Donations, Non-Union, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Correspondence re: Requests for Donations, Union, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Joe Abram and Associates, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: American Cancer Society, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: American Regal Association, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: City of Hope National Medical Center, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Greater Kansas City Golden Gloves, Inc., undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Correspondence re: IBT Invitational Golf Tournament, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Muscular Dystrophy Association [1/2], 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Correspondence: Muscular Dystrophy Association [2/2], 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Parity Foundation, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: Unico National, Kansas City Chapter, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: United Cerebral Palsy of New York City, Inc., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Correspondence re: Democratic, Republican, Independent Voter Education (DRIVE) Program, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Legal Papers Signed by Roy Williams, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Dwyer Costello and Co., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Roster Listings, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Murray Anderson: "The Thermonuclear Noble Gas Plasma Engine", undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Kentucky Colonels, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: The Wall Street Journal, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kansas City Community College Program for Adult College Education (PACE) Program, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Roy Williams Correspondence [1/2], 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Roy Williams Correspondence [2/2], 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- American Income Life Insurance Company "A.I. Labor Letter" Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Research Institute Recommendations, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- "The Future," Edited by Jack Anderson, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Periodicals and Newspapers Received, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: American Labor Beacon, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Correspondence re: 22nd International Convention [1/3], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Correspondence re: 22nd International Convention [2/3], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Correspondence re: 22nd International Convention [3/3], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Correspondence re: Election of Roy Williams as General President, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Teamsters Local 574 Election of Officers - Interview and Results, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Telegrams re: Out-of-Work Benefits [1/3], 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Telegrams re: Out-of-Work Benefits [2/3], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Telegrams re: Out-of-Work Benefits [3/3], 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Telegrams: General Executive Board, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- News Articles and Paper Clippings [1/3], 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- News Articles and Paper Clippings [2/3], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- News Articles and Paper Clippings [3/3], 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Jurisdictional Disputes, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- International Auditors List by State/Country, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Insurance Company Blank Forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- International Office Closure Notices, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Parking Garage Employees Seniority Plan, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Office Supplies Correspondence and Brochures, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- IBT Locals vs. Admiral Merchants Motor Freight, Inc. Court Case, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Correspondence re: Branch Motor Express Company, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Correspondence re: Convoy Express, Inc., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Emery Air Freight, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Correspondence re: Eazor Express, Inc., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Correspondence re: TIME-DC, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Correspondence re: IML Freight, Inc., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: The Kroger Company, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Lavatto Brothers, Inc., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: W.L. Logan Trucking Company, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Correspondence re: McLean Trucking (Meridian Express) Company, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Correspondence: Pacific Intermountain Express Company, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: Daniel Patrick Moynihan, National Labor Relations Board, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Schwerman Trucking Company, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Signal Delivery Service, Inc., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Correspondence re: Trucker Freight Lines, Inc., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Correspondence re: United Parcel Service, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Correspondence re: Walter and Smith Motor Freight, Inc., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Correspondence re: Wilson Freight, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Wycoff Company, Inc., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- United States vs. Michael Rudy Tham Case, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Correspondence re: Airline Industry, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Correspondence re: San Francisco Hotels for 1986 National Convention, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: American Trucking Associations, Inc., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Arkansas-Oklahoma Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Correspondence re: Armored Car Industry, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: National Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Trades Division, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Brewery and Soft Drink Workers Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Teamsters California State Council of Cannery and Food Processing Unions, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Carolina Freight Carriers Corporation, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Chicago Newspaper Reporters Association, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Industrial Trades Division, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Joint Labor Management Committee of the Retail Food Industry, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Correspondence: Baton Rouge oil and Chemical Workers Union, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Correspondence re: Public Employees' Trade Division, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: United Furniture Workers of America, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Joint Counci No. 2, Butte, MT, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: Joint Counil No. 7, San Francisco, CA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Correspondence: Joint Council No. 13, St. Louis, MO, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Correspondence: Joint Council No. 38, Sacramento, CA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Joint Council No. 41 Board Meeting Transcript, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Correspondence: Joint Council No. 43, Detriot, MI (re: Local 985), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Correspondence: Joint Council No. 53, Philadelphia, PA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Correspondence: Joint Council No. 56, Kansas City, MO, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Teamsters Local 26 (Danville, IL) Newsletters, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Correspondence: Local 41, Kansas City, MO, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Correspondence: Local 70, Oakland, CA, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Correspondence: Local 100, Cincinnati, OH, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Correspondence: Local 107, Philadelphia, PA, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Correspondence: Local 135, Indianapolis, IN, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Correspondence: Local 137, Redding, CA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Correspondence: Local 147, Des Moines, IA, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Correspondence: Local 214, Detroit, MI, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Correspondence: Local 215, Evansville, IN, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Teamsters Local 237 (New York, NY) Newsletters, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Correspondence: Local 238, Cedar Rapids, IA, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Correspondence: Local 283, Detroit, MI, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Correspondence: Local 710, Chicago, IL, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Correspondence re: Local 245, Springfield, MO, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: Local 299, Detroit, MI, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: Local 399, North Hollywood, CA, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Local 533, Sparks, NV, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Correspondence re: Local 560, Union City, NJ, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: Local 574, Cape Girardeau, MO, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Local 600, St. Louis, MO, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Correspondence: Local 662, Eau Claire, WI, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Local 682, St. Louis, MO, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: Local 695, Madison, WI, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Local 732, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Local 856, San Francisco, CA, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: Local 886, Oklahoma City, OK, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Local 891, Jackson, MS, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Local 952, Orange, CA, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Correspondence: Local 980, Santa Rosa, CA, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board Meeting - July 13, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- IBT Constitution Adopted by the 22nd International Convention, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Labor's Annual Directory and Buyer's Guide, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Central States, Southeast and Southwest Areas Retiree and Pension Plans, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Holiday Cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Teamsters Airline Division Report, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Canadian Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board Meeting - October 29, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Clerical Correspondence: Xerox, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Clerical Correspondence: Kessinger Hunter Realtors, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Clerical Correspondence re: General Office Supplies, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Clerical Correspondence: Monroe Calculators, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Clerical Correspondence: Southwestern Bell, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Financial Files, December 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Financial Files, November 1981, 1981 November (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Financial Files, October 1981, 1981 October (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Financial Files, September 1981, 1981 September (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Financial Files, August 1981, 1981 August (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Financial Files, July 1981, 1981 July (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Financial Files, January 1982, 1982 January (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Financial Files, February 1982, 1982 February (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Financial Files, March 1982, 1982 March (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Financial Files, April 1982, 1982 April (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Financial Files, May 1982, 1982 May (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Financial Files, June 1982, 1982 June (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Financial Files, July 1982, 1982 July (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Financial Files, August 1982, 1982 August (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Financial Files, September 1982, 1982 September (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Financial Files, October 1982, 1982 October (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Financial Files, November 1982, 1982 November (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Financial Files, December 1982, 1982 December (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Financial Files, January 1983, 1983 January (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Financial Files, March 1983, 1983 March (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Financial Files, April 1983, 1983 April (Box 13, Folder 9)
- National Steel Carriers' Association Grievance Cases [1/4], 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- National Steel Carriers' Association Grievance Cases [2/4], 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- National Steel Carriers' Association Grievance Cases [3/4], 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- National Steel Carriers' Association Grievance Cases [4/4], 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- National Freight Grievance Committee Rules of Procedure, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- National Freight Grievance Committee [1/2], 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- National Freight Grievance Committee [2/2], 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee New Post-Ratification Instructions, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- National Automobile Transporters Industry Negotiating Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- National Master Freight Agreement, Multi-Conference Carriers, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee Meeting Arrangements, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee Negotiations, Kansas City, MO, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- National Master Freight Agreements and Amendments [1/2], 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- National Master Freight Agreements and Amendments [2/2], 1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Correspondence: National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee [1/2], 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee [2/2], 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- National Master Freight Agreement Referendum, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: National Steel Carriers' Association, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: Arthur Bunte, Jr., Trucking Management, Inc., 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Frank Bridge, Motor Carrier Labor Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- "Comparison of National Master Freight Contract Changes Proposed by the National Freight Industry Negotiating Committee and by Trucking Management, Inc. with the Present National Master Freight Contract", 1981 November (Box 16, Folder 8)
- IBT 1982 National Master Freight Contract Ratification Results (Box 16, Folder 9)
- No-Raid Mutual Assistance Pacts, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: John Sullivan re: Unemployment, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Central Conference of Teamsters Policy Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Central Conference of Teamsters, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Central States Area Iron and Steel and Special Commodities Rider, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Western Conference of Teamsters Financial Statements, January 1 - December 31, 1981, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Clerical Correspondence: Quality Medical Systems, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Clerical Correspondence: Haren and Laughlin Construction Company, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Clerical Correspondence: Silverleaf Plants, Inc., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Clerical Correspondence: Time, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Clerical Correspondence: Titan, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Clerical Correspondence: Thomas Havey and Co, Certified Public Accountants, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Clerical Correspondence: Best Sign Systems, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Clerical Correspondence: Demaree Stationary Company, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Clerical Correspondence: Fortune Magazine, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Clerical Correspondence: Mark's Parking Stations, Inc., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Clerical Correspondence: Mosler Record Safes, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Clerical Correspondence: Necco Coffee, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Clerical Correspondence: Peters and Associates, Inc., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Clerical Correspondence: ABC Interiors, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Advertisements, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Telephone and Room Number Directory, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- IBT Industrial Trades Division Conference Summary, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board Meeting - January 19, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- National Master Freight Agreement Summaries of Changes, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Correspondence re: Central States Pension Fund, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Correspondence re: Support for Roy Williams in Bribery Case, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Roy Williams Bribery Case Legal Fees, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- United States vs. Dorfman, et al (Roy Williams Bribery Case) [1/2], 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)